{
    "subject": "resource/Voice_of_OC",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/Santa_Ana,_California",
    "human_readable": "The location of Voice of OC is Santa Ana, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9218947291374207,
            "question": "Is Voice of OC located in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8218362331390381,
            "question": "Where is Voice of OC located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.715121328830719,
            "question": "Can you tell me the location of Voice of OC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6335573792457581,
            "question": "In which state can you find Voice of OC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6057210564613342,
            "question": "Where are the offices of Voice of OC situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5930200815200806,
            "question": "What city and state is Voice of OC in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5880600810050964,
            "question": "In which city does Voice of OC operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.538483738899231,
            "question": "What is the city headquarters for Voice of OC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41844847798347473,
            "question": "What is the address of Voice of OC's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2225707769393921,
            "question": "Santa Ana, California is home to what organization?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of Voice of OC is Santa Ana, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7664_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the address of Voice of OC's headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7664_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the city headquarters for Voice of OC?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7664_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which city does Voice of OC operate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7664_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7664_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided that Voice Of OC is based in Santa Ana, CA."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}